https://specialtyfoodsgroup.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy states the terms under which information about you is collected and used when accessing www.specialtyfoodsgroup.com (the “Site”). By accessing the Site you agree to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice by posting the modified Privacy Policy here. You should check this Privacy Policy each time you visit the Site to identify and understand any changes made since your previous visit. By continuing to access or use the Site, you agree to be bound by any modifications to this Privacy Policy. Please consult our Legal Terms and Conditions for additional terms and conditions that apply to your use and access to the Site.
Information You Submit
At Specialty Foods Group, LLC. “SFG” your privacy is important to us. SFG does not collect personally identifying information about you, which includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address (“Personally Identifying Information”), unless you voluntarily submit it to us through one of our Information Collection Forms, or by e-mail or other means.
Information We Gather Automatically
When you visit our Site, we may automatically collect certain non-identifying information about you, such as your movement about the site or the pages on the site you visit most frequently, the type of browser or computer operating system you use or the domain name of the Site from which you linked to us (“Non-identifying Information”). In addition, we may store small files on your computer’s hard drive as a “cookie” or similar type of file to track and target your interests. We use this Non-identifying Information internally, to help us enhance the efficiency and usefulness of the Site and to improve customer service. If you object to this practice, please consult your browser’s documentation for instructions on erasing or blocking cookies.
Additional Privacy Protections for Children This Site is not aimed at children less than 18 years of age. Any information submitted through the Information Collection Form pages that we know or reasonably believe originated from a child less than 18 years of age will be deleted. Children should never reveal their addresses, phone numbers or other Personally Identifying Information to any strangers on the Internet.
Use of Information
Any Personally Identifying Information or Non-identifying Information (hereinafter collectively “Information”) we gather, whether voluntarily provided by you or automatically collected, may be used for our internal business and marketing purposes. We do not sell or otherwise disclose such Information to third parties except as necessary to achieve the purpose for which the Information was submitted or collected, or to comply with the law, law enforcement agencies, or legal process served on SFG, or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is necessary to defend our rights or property or to respond to an emergency situation.
Links to Third Party Websites
This Site contains links to other websites owned and operated by third parties. Please note that these sites’ privacy policies may differ from that of SFG. SFG is not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties and does not control use of Information provided through such third party sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any website you may visit.
Security
SFG has reasonable security measures in place to protect the Personally Identifying Information you submit to us, once it is received, but we cannot be responsible for the security of information in transit. We have taken careful measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your Personally Identifying Information. Once we receive your Personally Identifying Information that was entered into our Site, it is stored behind a firewall. Your Personally Identifying Information is only accessible to those employees who need it in order to perform their jobs. When you communicate with SFG by e-mail, however, your communication is not necessarily secure from interception and is subject to all of the risks of electronic communication. SFG does not guarantee the security or confidentiality of transmissions. SFG reserves the right to update or otherwise alter our security practices if and when it seems appropriate.
Community Values
Contact Us
Careers at SFG
Industry Solutions
Brand and Sales Resources
Copyright © 2020 SFG, LLC and its Affiliated Companies. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy | Do Not Sell My Personal Information | Latest Covid-19 Information
